<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitOps on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/gitops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitOps on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:00:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/gitops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS Modernization Workshop With GitOps and Codefresh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/codefresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/codefresh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn about GitOps deployments in a cloud environment and more specifically on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gitlab DevOps Modernization Workshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-cicd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-cicd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn about the GitLab DevOps platform and how to build, test, and deploy features and functionality at a faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate GitOps - Deploy Secure Microservices to AWS EKS with the GitLab Agent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn to use the new GitLab Agent for Kubernetes to integrate with EKS more securely and to add GitOps pull deployments. Add GitLab’s mature DevSecOps security scanning, automated review environment management and cluster scanning security to your latest GitOps projects. Learn how the new GitLab Agent cluster connection method improves the security posture for all existing EKS CD push integrations as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitOps on EKS with Weaveworks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/weaveworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 17:14:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/weaveworks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In these workshop modules Weaveworks will introduce you to GitOps on EKS including an introduction to the 4 principles of GitOps, building reliable EKS enviroments, incorporating security, accelerating software development and managing Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence models w/GitOps on EKS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
