<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevSecOps on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/devsecops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevSecOps on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:10:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/devsecops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps Protection with Trend Micro - Cloud One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-devsecops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-devsecops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage the Cloud One Platform to enforce the detection and protection in Applications, Elastic Kubernetes Service, Open-Source Projects and your IaC Templates!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing your Data Migration to AWS S3 with Trend Micro Cloud One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-datamigr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-datamigr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to migrate your objects from a on-premise Network File Server (NFS) using AWS DataSync to AWS S3 in your AWS account securing the files with Trend Micro Cloud One File Storage Security.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline Security Operations and Management with Trend Micro - Cloud One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-security/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage Cloud One - Workload Security to enforce the detection and protection policy (application control, anti-malware, Hosted IDS/IPS, firewall, integrity monitoring, and log inspection) via a small software component deployed on each instance being protected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an Extra Network Layer of Protection with Your AWS Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-net/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to leverage Trend Micro Cloud One – Network Security to protect the connectivity from the internet to your applications running on Amazon EC2, ECS, AWS Fargate and others. Cloud workloads frequently require internet access, and as we know, anything accessing the internet can be breached. This workshop explores simple tactics on how to protect the internet connectivity to your AWS services and between VPCs. In this workshop, you will learn how to protect your cloud network and meet compliance requirements such as PCI, DSS and HIPAA to deploy Network IDS/IPS into your AWS environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Workshops with Sumo Logic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/sumologic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/sumologic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to monitor data visualization and AWS application observability using Sumo Logic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Modernization Application with Security Embedded - DevSecOps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-appsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-appsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to leverage Trend Micro Cloud One - Application Security with your serverless applications running on AWS Lambda or containerized applications running on AWS Fargate. If you looking to make cloud security more efficient, proactive, and gain visibility to help lead your developers, cloud architects, and DevOps engineers, this workshop is for you! Bridge the gap between your security and development teams by providing relevant information to gain better visibility into attacks targeting your cloud native applications, and take security action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Security Visibility with Trend Micro &amp; Snyk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudone-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudone-oss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to scan your projects on git repository and easily see the open source vulnerabilities existing in the open source projects that you applications are using. You will learn how you shift-left security leveraging Cloud One - Open Source Security by Snyk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate GitOps - Deploy Secure Microservices to AWS EKS with the GitLab Agent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn to use the new GitLab Agent for Kubernetes to integrate with EKS more securely and to add GitOps pull deployments. Add GitLab’s mature DevSecOps security scanning, automated review environment management and cluster scanning security to your latest GitOps projects. Learn how the new GitLab Agent cluster connection method improves the security posture for all existing EKS CD push integrations as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro S3 Malware Scanning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-s3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to scan your objects stored in Amazon S3 buckets against malware and integrate them into your custom workflows by automating with your current resources, directly into your AWS environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AWS Infrastructure with Trend Micro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage infrastructure as code (IaC) and Security to automate your cloud security efforts. If you’re interested in making cloud security more efficient, automated, proactive, and accessible to developers, cloud architects, DevOps engineers this workshop is for you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Aqua</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/aqua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/aqua/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to secure your workloads on Amazon EKS using Aqua&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive DevSecOps platform and tooling&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with CircleCI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/circleci/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/circleci/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn why DevOps is a pattern for modernization and how to use patterns with CircleCI to release features and functionality at a faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with AWS &amp; Snyk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/container-snyk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/container-snyk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to scan containerized applications on Amazon EKS with Snyk. We will learn about Open Source vulnerabilities introduced by your Container Base Image and your application dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
