<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VPC on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/vpc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VPC on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:10:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/vpc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps Protection with Trend Micro - Cloud One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-devsecops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-devsecops/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage the Cloud One Platform to enforce the detection and protection in Applications, Elastic Kubernetes Service, Open-Source Projects and your IaC Templates!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Check Point CloudGuard Network Security and AWS Gateway Load Balancer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/checkpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/checkpoint/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Secure, Control, &amp; Own Your Data with VGS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/vgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/vgs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn why DevOps and DevSecOps teams are turning to Data Security as a Service (DSaaS) providers, like Very Good Security (VGS), to secure sensitive data, streamline their workflows, and descope sensitive data from their tech stack to accelerate their journey to information security compliances like PCI DSS, SOC 2, GDPR, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating an Extra Network Layer of Protection with Your AWS Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-cloudone-net/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to leverage Trend Micro Cloud One – Network Security to protect the connectivity from the internet to your applications running on Amazon EC2, ECS, AWS Fargate and others. Cloud workloads frequently require internet access, and as we know, anything accessing the internet can be breached. This workshop explores simple tactics on how to protect the internet connectivity to your AWS services and between VPCs. In this workshop, you will learn how to protect your cloud network and meet compliance requirements such as PCI, DSS and HIPAA to deploy Network IDS/IPS into your AWS environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Valtix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/valtix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/valtix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn why DevOps is a pattern for modernization and how to use patterns with Valtix to release features and functionality at a faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
