<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Serverless on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/serverless/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Serverless on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:10:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/serverless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Serverless SaaS Workshop with Fauna</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/fauna/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 20:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/fauna/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will be building a multi-tenant Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) solution using Fauna and AWS Serverless Services, specifically Amazon API Gateway, Amazon Cognito, AWS Lambda, AWS CodePipeline, and Amazon CloudWatch. The goal is to provide an understanding of serverless architecture as it apples to multi-tenancy, and introduce Fauna features/functionality that make them seamless to implement&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Momento</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/momentohq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/momentohq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, learn the simplicity of enhancing DynamoDB performance through caching and activating real-time notifications with Momento Cache and Topics. Dive into these lessons by updating an online pizza shop&amp;rsquo;s order processing system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernize Applications to AWS Architectures with CAST Imaging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-imaging/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture the bug using Elasticsearch Service on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this hands-on workshop you will learn how to use Elasticsearch Service in your AWS environment. We will automatically create the full environment for you including an example application. Your task will be to identify issues within this application by using Elasticsearch, to solve these issues, and finally to get an idea about usage. By the end of the workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a solid understanding of how to effectively use Elasticsearch to improve your AWS based applications and infrastructure, and gain valuable insights into usage patterns. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this unique opportunity to level up your skills and take your Elasticsearch on AWS expertise to the next level!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Portfolio Modernization with CAST Highlight</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-software/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless ASP.NET Framework Modernization Workshop with Stackery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/stackery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/stackery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a workshop to demonstrate how to modernize an ASP.NET REST API service, which runs on expensive, inflexible Windows servers in the cloud, into a resilient, highly scalable serverless service. The approach utilizes the Strangler Fig Pattern to modernize the application piece-by-piece rather than rewrite the entire application all at once.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debug serverless applications with Lumigo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/lumigo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 15:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/lumigo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to gain observability into your serverless application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless Observability with AppDynamics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/appd-serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/appd-serverless/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gain hands-on experience using AppDynamics, an AWS advanced technology ISV Partner, to add observability and monitoring to the serverless components of a microservices-based application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applied Observability for Modern Applications with Epsagon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/epsagon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 17:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/epsagon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to gain observability into your serverless application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Relic One - Serverless</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic-serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:13:53 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic-serverless/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to achieve application observability using New Relic One on AWS with serverless services such as AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon API Gateway, and other AWS services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
