<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Datasaur LLM Labs AWS Workshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/datasaur/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/datasaur/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right size workload resources on Amazon EKS with Stormforge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/stormforge-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/stormforge-io/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how StormForge Optimize Live can be used to continuously rightsize Kubernetes workloads. With this knowledge, you can ensure that your cloud-native applications are both cost effective and performant while removing developer toil.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logz.io Observability &amp; Security for Teams that Love Open Source</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/logz-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/logz-io/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn about the importance of observabilty in in modern software development and operations.&#xA;You’ll also have practical knowledge of how to implement observability in your own systems and how to use it to detect and diagnose issues quickly and effectively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernize Applications to AWS Architectures with CAST Imaging</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-imaging/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 23:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-imaging/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubleshooting Amazon EKS Applications with Lightrun Dynamic Observability Platform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/lightrun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:15:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/lightrun/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture the bug using Elasticsearch Service on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this hands-on workshop you will learn how to use Elasticsearch Service in your AWS environment. We will automatically create the full environment for you including an example application. Your task will be to identify issues within this application by using Elasticsearch, to solve these issues, and finally to get an idea about usage. By the end of the workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a solid understanding of how to effectively use Elasticsearch to improve your AWS based applications and infrastructure, and gain valuable insights into usage patterns. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this unique opportunity to level up your skills and take your Elasticsearch on AWS expertise to the next level!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Portfolio Modernization with CAST Highlight</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cast-software/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing IAC with Synk and Hashicorp</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/securing-iac-synk-and-hashicorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/securing-iac-synk-and-hashicorp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Secure, Control, &amp; Own Your Data with VGS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/vgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/vgs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn why DevOps and DevSecOps teams are turning to Data Security as a Service (DSaaS) providers, like Very Good Security (VGS), to secure sensitive data, streamline their workflows, and descope sensitive data from their tech stack to accelerate their journey to information security compliances like PCI DSS, SOC 2, GDPR, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Account and Workload Security with Lacework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/lacework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/lacework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn about securing the software delivery process, implementing security operation workflows on AWS, and managing security across accounts with Lacework Cloud Security Platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Modernization Application with Security Embedded - DevSecOps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-appsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-appsec/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to leverage Trend Micro Cloud One - Application Security with your serverless applications running on AWS Lambda or containerized applications running on AWS Fargate. If you looking to make cloud security more efficient, proactive, and gain visibility to help lead your developers, cloud architects, and DevOps engineers, this workshop is for you! Bridge the gap between your security and development teams by providing relevant information to gain better visibility into attacks targeting your cloud native applications, and take security action.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Marketplace DevOps Workshop Series Hands-on Lab with CloudBees Feature Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudbees-fm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 11:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudbees-fm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to use CloudBees Feature Management to decouple deployments from releases, experiment with testing on production to improve feedback loops and leverage GitOps to seamlessly synchronize states of feature flags.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Modernization Workshop with HashiCorp Terraform Cloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/hashicorp-terraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 11:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/hashicorp-terraform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Get hands-on experience using HashiCorp Terraform Cloud to deploy infrastructure as code in AWS and leverage Sentinel policy-as-code to enable fine-grained, logic-based policy decision. By completing this lab you will learn how to leverage HashiCorp Terraform Cloud and Sentinel for easier deployments of your applications and infrastructure in AWS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Modernization Workshop With GitOps and Codefresh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/codefresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:00:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/codefresh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn about GitOps deployments in a cloud environment and more specifically on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Security Visibility with Trend Micro &amp; Snyk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudone-oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:08:22 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cloudone-oss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to scan your projects on git repository and easily see the open source vulnerabilities existing in the open source projects that you applications are using. You will learn how you shift-left security leveraging Cloud One - Open Source Security by Snyk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gitlab DevOps Modernization Workshop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-cicd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-cicd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn about the GitLab DevOps platform and how to build, test, and deploy features and functionality at a faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident managment and response with Pagerduty</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/pagerduty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/pagerduty/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how Pagerduty helps with incident managment and response, and how to imporve your teams incident managment levraging AWS integration.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate GitOps - Deploy Secure Microservices to AWS EKS with the GitLab Agent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:30:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gitlab-for-eks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn to use the new GitLab Agent for Kubernetes to integrate with EKS more securely and to add GitOps pull deployments. Add GitLab’s mature DevSecOps security scanning, automated review environment management and cluster scanning security to your latest GitOps projects. Learn how the new GitLab Agent cluster connection method improves the security posture for all existing EKS CD push integrations as well.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observability with Amazon EKS and Pixie by New Relic One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to add Observability and troubleshoot issues in Amazon EKS Cluster using Pixie by New Relic One.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Functional Test Automation with Micro Focus UFT One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/microfocus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/microfocus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This workshop will show you how to use UFT One to design an AI-based functional test of a web application, run the test, and understand the details of each step executed during the test run.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale Android tests with Genymotion</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/genymotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/genymotion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to improve your Android testing infrastructure and scale up and down your tests with Genymotion Android virtual devices&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn about securing CloudFormation templates from code to cloud using Bridgecrew’s integrations with VS Code, CodeBuild, CodePipeline, GitHub and AWS runtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Bridgecrew and Terraform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrewterraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrewterraform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn about securing Terraform templates from code to cloud using Bridgecrew’s integrations with VS Code, GitHub, Terraform Cloud, and AWS runtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro S3 Malware Scanning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro-s3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to scan your objects stored in Amazon S3 buckets against malware and integrate them into your custom workflows by automating with your current resources, directly into your AWS environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AWS Infrastructure with Trend Micro</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/trendmicro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage infrastructure as code (IaC) and Security to automate your cloud security efforts. If you’re interested in making cloud security more efficient, automated, proactive, and accessible to developers, cloud architects, DevOps engineers this workshop is for you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Armory</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/armory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/armory/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to use Armory to provision an EKS Cluster and configure different deployment types as well as how to scale and rollback deployments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Tigera</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/tigera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/tigera/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to design, deploy, and observe security and networking policies in an EKS environment using Calico&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Valtix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/valtix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/valtix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn why DevOps is a pattern for modernization and how to use patterns with Valtix to release features and functionality at a faster pace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Modernization Workshop with Harness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/harness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 13:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/harness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will gain hands-on experience using Harness to deploy an application to AWS EKS. Harness is a self-service CI/CD platform that allows engineers and DevOps team to build, test, deploy, and verify software, on-demand. This is a hands-on workshop where you will learn how to leverage Harness for easier deployments of your application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless ASP.NET Framework Modernization Workshop with Stackery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/stackery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 15:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/stackery/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a workshop to demonstrate how to modernize an ASP.NET REST API service, which runs on expensive, inflexible Windows servers in the cloud, into a resilient, highly scalable serverless service. The approach utilizes the Strangler Fig Pattern to modernize the application piece-by-piece rather than rewrite the entire application all at once.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application modernization with AWS and Docker</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/docker-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 10:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/docker-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this hands on session, we will take a sample two tier application and use Docker Compose to power up local development on AWS Elastic Container Service (ECS) and then to deploy to AWS Cloud, all with a consistent developer experience using Docker Compose CLI. During the session, we will uncover how to embed your existing services in the compose file and simulate a real world scenario by fine tuning your AWS Cloudformation templates using docker compose overlays and finally orchestrate continuous deployment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Devops with AWS &amp; Sysdig</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/sysdig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/sysdig/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to securely run cloud applications in production by automating AWS Fargate and ECR image scanning directly in your AWS environment. You will also learn how to improve the security of your cloud infrastructure using AWS CloudTrail and Sysdig CloudConnector.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Automation at Scale with Quali</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/quali/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/quali/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gain hands-on experience with Quali, an AWS advanced technology ISV partner, to automatically deploy and release an e-commerce application as part of your DevOps practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serverless Observability with AppDynamics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/appd-serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 08:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/appd-serverless/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gain hands-on experience using AppDynamics, an AWS advanced technology ISV Partner, to add observability and monitoring to the serverless components of a microservices-based application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Modernization with JFrog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/jfrog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/jfrog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn about the JFrog Platform and how to leverage Artifactory and JFrog Xray for managing your Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) and bring DevOps to the cloud on AWS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a modern architecture with GitLab, Hashicorp and Gremlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/ghg_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/ghg_workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop we will work with GitLab, Hashicorp and Gremlin to show how to detect single points of failure within a gitflow deployment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos Engineering with Gremlin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/gremlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/gremlin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will get a hands-on introduction to Chaos Engineering by assuming the role of Mystical Mysfit’s newest site reliability engineer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Infrastructure as Code with Pulumi</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/pulumi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/pulumi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This workshop teaches you “Modern” Infrastructure as Code (IaC) concepts through a series of hands-on labs, using Pulumi.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Automation with Cognizant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/cognizant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 14:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/cognizant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn from Cognizant how to continuously test an application along different portions of the DevOps CI/CD lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Atlassian &amp; Snyk</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/snyk-atlassian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/snyk-atlassian/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn patterns for shift-left security leveraging Atlassian Bitbucket, Bitbucket Pipelines, and Snyk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenShift 4 on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/redhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/redhat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you are able to explore OpenShift and its role in modernization. The features which cater for better developer productivity and reduce operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will also explore lift and shift or workloads from on premises to the cloud, modernization of workloads using native AWS services and how Service broker, operators and AWS servcie catalog form a part of this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees can complete the entire workshop or focus on a track specific to their role.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCF on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/pivotal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 18:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/pivotal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will Pivotal Cloud Foundry on AWS, deploying application workloads, deploying and using integrations such as the AWS Service Broker for modernizaing applications with native AWS services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/contrastsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 22:05:01 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/contrastsecurity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how Contrast technology platform is a fundamentally new way to protect a company from threats, giving our customers visibility and accuracy into their applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
