<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DynamoDB on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dynamodb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DynamoDB on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:10:07 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dynamodb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Momento</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/momentohq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/momentohq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, learn the simplicity of enhancing DynamoDB performance through caching and activating real-time notifications with Momento Cache and Topics. Dive into these lessons by updating an online pizza shop&amp;rsquo;s order processing system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture the bug using Elasticsearch Service on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this hands-on workshop you will learn how to use Elasticsearch Service in your AWS environment. We will automatically create the full environment for you including an example application. Your task will be to identify issues within this application by using Elasticsearch, to solve these issues, and finally to get an idea about usage. By the end of the workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a solid understanding of how to effectively use Elasticsearch to improve your AWS based applications and infrastructure, and gain valuable insights into usage patterns. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this unique opportunity to level up your skills and take your Elasticsearch on AWS expertise to the next level!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Real-time Dashboards with Rockset, DynamoDB, and Grafana</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/rockset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/rockset/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how rockset, empowers analysts and business users to query live data. Participants will be guided through ingesting data from dynamodb to rockset. Along the way, they will query live data and combine it with static data in S3.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Workshops with Sumo Logic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/sumologic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/sumologic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn how to monitor data visualization and AWS application observability using Sumo Logic.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debug serverless applications with Lumigo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/lumigo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 15:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/lumigo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to gain observability into your serverless application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applied Observability for Modern Applications with Epsagon</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/epsagon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 17:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/epsagon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you’ll learn how to gain observability into your serverless application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Relic One - Serverless</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic-serverless/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 16:13:53 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/newrelic-serverless/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn how to achieve application observability using New Relic One on AWS with serverless services such as AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon API Gateway, and other AWS services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
