<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CloudFormation on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/cloudformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CloudFormation on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:10:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/cloudformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Capture the bug using Elasticsearch Service on AWS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:10:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/elastic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this hands-on workshop you will learn how to use Elasticsearch Service in your AWS environment. We will automatically create the full environment for you including an example application. Your task will be to identify issues within this application by using Elasticsearch, to solve these issues, and finally to get an idea about usage. By the end of the workshop, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a solid understanding of how to effectively use Elasticsearch to improve your AWS based applications and infrastructure, and gain valuable insights into usage patterns. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this unique opportunity to level up your skills and take your Elasticsearch on AWS expertise to the next level!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Account and Workload Security with Lacework</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/lacework/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/lacework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn about securing the software delivery process, implementing security operation workflows on AWS, and managing security across accounts with Lacework Cloud Security Platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data in Motion applications with Confluent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/confluent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/confluent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this workshop you will learn how to use fully-managed Confluent Cloud on AWS to source historical data into Kafka, accept streaming credit applications in real time and use ksqlDB to process data together and generate request outcome.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/card/bridgecrew/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learn about securing CloudFormation templates from code to cloud using Bridgecrew’s integrations with VS Code, CodeBuild, CodePipeline, GitHub and AWS runtime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
