<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security on Modernization workshop</title>
    <link>https://awsworkshop.io/categories/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security on Modernization workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://awsworkshop.io/categories/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS environments with superwerker</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/superwerker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/superwerker/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you will learn how to navigate in a multi-account AWS environment set up with superwerker. Companies of all sizes can benefit from deploying with superwerker. Start-ups and small-to-medium businesses can especially benefit when time-to-market and financial aspects are concerns. Regardless of company size, superwerker lets you run your business without spending excess time setting up and maintaining your AWS Cloud environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Bridgecrew</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/bridgecrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/bridgecrew/</guid>
      <description>Learn about securing CloudFormation templates from code to cloud using Bridgecrew’s integrations with VS Code, CodeBuild, CodePipeline, GitHub and AWS runtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Bridgecrew and Terraform</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/bridgecrewterraform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/bridgecrewterraform/</guid>
      <description>Learn about securing Terraform templates from code to cloud using Bridgecrew’s integrations with VS Code, GitHub, Terraform Cloud, and AWS runtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trend Micro S3 Malware Scanning</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/trendmicro-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/trendmicro-s3/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you will learn how to scan your objects stored in Amazon S3 buckets against malware and integrate them into your custom workflows by automating with your current resources, directly into your AWS environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securing AWS Infrastructure with Trend Micro</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/trendmicro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:15:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/trendmicro/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you’ll learn how to leverage infrastructure as code (IaC) and Security to automate your cloud security efforts. If you’re interested in making cloud security more efficient, automated, proactive, and accessible to developers, cloud architects, DevOps engineers this workshop is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Aqua</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/aqua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/aqua/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop you will learn how to secure your workloads on Amazon EKS using Aqua&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive DevSecOps platform and tooling</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with Tigera</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/tigera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/tigera/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop you will learn how to design, deploy, and observe security and networking policies in an EKS environment using Calico</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization with AWS, Snyk and Docker</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/docker-snyk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 08:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/docker-snyk/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop you will learn how to scan containerized applications on Amazon EKS using the Docker CLI tool developed in partnership with Snyk and Docker. We will learn about Open Source vulnerabilities introduced by your Container Base Image and your application dependencies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Devops with AWS &amp; Sysdig</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/sysdig/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/sysdig/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you will learn how to securely run cloud applications in production by automating AWS Fargate and ECR image scanning directly in your AWS environment. You will also learn how to improve the security of your cloud infrastructure using AWS CloudTrail and Sysdig CloudConnector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Modernization with JFrog</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/jfrog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:46:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/jfrog/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop you will learn about the JFrog Platform and how to leverage Artifactory and JFrog Xray for managing your Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) and bring DevOps to the cloud on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevSecOps with Atlassian &amp; Snyk</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/snyk-atlassian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 20:10:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/snyk-atlassian/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you will learn patterns for shift-left security leveraging Atlassian Bitbucket, Bitbucket Pipelines, and Snyk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.Net Core Container Secrets</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/dotnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 18:53:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/dotnet/</guid>
      <description>In this module, you will learn how to containerize an existing .Net application and implement modern cloud based security principles to secure your application in production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snyk</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/snyk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 18:40:47 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/snyk/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop, you will learn how to add security testing to a CI/CD pipeline of a dockerized application using AWS CodeCommit, AWS CodeBuild, and AWS CodePipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contrast Security</title>
      <link>https://awsworkshop.io/card/contrastsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 22:05:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awsworkshop.io/card/contrastsecurity/</guid>
      <description>In this workshop you will learn how Contrast technology platform is a fundamentally new way to protect a company from threats, giving our customers visibility and accuracy into their applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
